

# Tomáš Javorský

### **About Me**

I'm an IT developer focused on front end web development in React and Node.js ecosystem. In the past, I have worked in different IT fields, ranging from game deveopment in Unity, trough mobile application in native Android all the way to front end development in React. I have received a Master's degree in Computer Science, however, most of my skills are self taught. I am a fast learner and my proficiency in various programming fields together with skill in 2D and 3D graphical software makes me a very versatile asset to any team.

## Education

Master's degree in Service Science, Management, and Engineering Faculty of Informatics Masaryk University - 2018 Thesis: Body Transfer Illusion in VR - https://is.muni.cz/th/y73cq/

## Experience

### **React Developer at COD8**

Coding various Front-end web applications in React and mobile apps in React Native. 2021 - present - cod8.io

## React Developer at Shipmonk

Coding front-end of fulfillment management web application in React, with Redux and Material UI. 2020 - 2020 - shipmonk.com

#### React Developer at QEST

Coding front-end of web file manager in React, with Redux and Styled Components. Tested using Jest and React testing library 2019 - 2020 - gest.cz

#### **React + Node.js Developer**

2019 - 2019

#### **Unity Dev at Powerplay Studio**

2017 - 2019 - powerplay.studio

#### **Android Dev at Reinto**

2016 - 2017 - reinto.cz





React React Native

























**English** 



## **Volunteering**

### **Erasmus Student Network**

Masaryk University - 2015 - 2017

## Preservation of enviroment

Workcamps by IJGD, SIW and NICE Hann. Münden - Germany - 2006 Ameland - Holland - 2007 Gevelsberg - Germany - 2008 Shiiba - Japan - 2014

## Links



tomasjavorsky.github.io



linkedin.com/in/tomasjavorsky







tomus.dev@gmail.com



Prague, Czech Republic